Christopher A Jones

Front End Developer Wethersfield , CT 860-301-7554

CJones4225@gmail.com

GitHub: CJones4225

Summary:

A highly-motivated, analytical and professional programmer interested in working for Infosys. My experience includes AngularJS, Javascript, React, HTML/CSS, and more. I'm also versed in the ServiceNow platform and Agile methodology. With the help and guidance of this interim program, I hope to begin a long and rewarding career with Infosys.

Education:

New Apprenticeship Bootcamp February 2022 - April 2022

Three Rivers Community College, Norwich, CT Associate Degree in Computer Science 2020

NuCamp Coding Bootcamp Coding Bootcamp: Front end Web & Mobile Development 2021

Summary of Skills:

- React
- AngularJS
- Javascript

- HTML / CSS
- ServiceNow
- Enterprise COBOL (Z/OS)

Work Experience:

Bar Porter

Foxwoods, Ladyard, CT

2005 - 2022

- Analyzed and forecasted inventory
- Warehouse delivery & pickup

- Stocked bars
- Cleaned

Mainframe Programmer

Bank of America, Hartford, CT

1998 - 2004

- Handled Production Support
- Complete Product Life Cycle
- Implemented new accounts
- Coordinated Disaster Recovery

- Facilitated contact business line
- Used Mainframe tools
- CICS / TSO / VSAM / DB2
- JCL, Cobol, Changeman, Easytrieve